We can beat them.
Joey, who is your boyfriend
or suitor?
Oh, no. Those three are really
competitive.
And they're working out.
They're showing off
their physiques.
Don't look at them!
Joey, I have a question.
So among the three of us,
who has the best body?
That's right,
it should be like that,
and not fighting
with each other,
and taking your clothes off.
It's embarrassing for the kids.
I'm sorry.
We promised them
that we would do our best.
Well, I'm happy that we're on
the same side today
because I'm not used to being on
the same side.
And you're happier
when I'm by your side...
I mean, the three of us.
You know, because you were so
focused on being so competitive,
the kid got hurt.
When luck is on our side,
both mother and daughter
are together.
Someone's coming, Boss.
Let's leave.
The other guy is Berdugo's
brother-in-law.
He can't see me.
- Hey!
- Hey...
Could it be that my daughter
and I are their targets?
Maybe this is related
to my husband's case.
This is kind of weird for me.
I'm not used to having friends.
You know, it's hard to find real
friends.
That's why we should take care
of our friendship, right?
Theresa...
It's not just about me and you.
I have to protect my friends.
I have to protect Joey.
Sorry, Miss Delgado.
The court did not accept
the witness statement
due to technicalities.
What?
Buddy,
I heard you have a new witness
in your case.
Where did you hear that?
We have a saying here inside.
The news outside seeps through
the bars.
What? Do you have a big chance?
Or maybe you've been acquitted?
You don't need the information
you asked me
for about Berdugo anymore.
I still need it.
You really still plan
to clash with Berdugo's group
even though you're free.
I don't know if there's
something really wrong
with your head.
I'll decide what to do
with that information.
What?
Will you keep your promise
or not?
I have one word.
I don't have the
information right now,
but I'll give it to you.
If I were you, I'd hurry up
with your coffee there.
The jail guard is coming.
Where is it?
Because there is no supporting
evidence,
everything Golda said in court
was considered hearsay.
So, what now?
Well, maybe the decision could
be changed
if we talk to the judge.
Joey, I don't think we can do
that at this point.
Actually, I think someone
already talked to the judge,
which is why he made
the decision that way.
Maybe someone sabotaged
our case.
It's Berdugo.
His connections are really wide,
Joey.
We can't beat him.
So...
What now? Nothing?
That's just gone?
Is it over?
There's nothing we can do?
If Golda's statement
can't be used,
how can Father be free?
What are we going to do, Andrew?
Everything we worked hard for...
everything we worked hard for,
is gone?
Joey...
Hello, Mother?
Have you heard about father's
case?
I talked to the attorney
earlier, Joey.
I already know what happened.
Why is this happening to us,
Mom?
We looked for Golda
for a long time.
I've been going through so much
just to get her to testify,
and then they'll just
throw it away.
What's that?
All my sacrifices are gone?
It's not like that, Joey.
If it weren't for what you did,
I wouldn't know the truth.
That Golda and your Father
didn't have an affair.
But, Mother, what about Father
now?
We have no way out of his case.
Joey, don't lose hope.
God has mercy.
I also believe that.
He listens to our prayers.
Our family will be reunited.
It will happen.
So just hold on, my child, okay?
So that's Berdugo's plan.
To bribe the judge.
That's great.
Everything has a price.
You just need to know how much.
Well, at least Berdugo is happy.
Delgado will have nothing
to look forward to,
and his case will have
no way out,
and he'll rot in jail.
Exactly!
Joey?
What are you doing?
Researching.
Researching...
Wait, did you sleep yet?
Now that Golda's testimony
is no longer valid,
I need to find another strategy
to help my father.
I understand where you're coming
from, Joey.
I know you really want
to help your father.
But you should know that
he has an attorney,
and he knows what to do.
Andrew, it's hard to hope again.
What if father's attorney
doesn't have a defense?
You know, I'm so confused
just thinking about it.
I don't know what to do
to help my father.
Honestly, I'm really
having a hard time, Andrew.
I just really want to help Joey.
But how, Boss?
You did everything already.
You're so involved in that case.
I know,
but I can't just back out,
right?
You know, honestly,
I feel like a miracle is all
that will help me...
unless you have a suggestion.
Guys! Guys! Stop talking.
Listen to what I have to say.
No one is talking here.
You spoke.
No, this is more important.
Go ahead. Go, what's that?
My vlogger friend texted.
There's a big scoop,
as in a really big one.
But now, we need to go
to Bolagos Lake.
Wait, why are we going
to Bolagos?
That's a lot.
Sir, who saw that?
They said it was divers
who were vlogging.
They're giving statements
at the precinct.
With so many of them,
we suspect that these people
are victims of a syndicate.
This is the diver vloggers'
first time
visiting Bolagos Lake.
The vloggers' intention
was to provide entertaining
and educational content,
but what surprised them
was a disgusting sight.
According to the police,
additional weights were placed
in the bags
containing the bodies so that
they would not rise and float.
This is just an example,
not the actual bag.
The Bolagos Police promise
to identify the bodies found
and find out what really
happened to them
and who should be held
responsible for the deaths
of the victims.
Only a demon would do that.
The victims and their families
are pitiful.
Have a drink first.
Did you see it, Mom?
The bodies are in the bag.
We saw it on social media.
That's terrible, Hon.
It's horrifying!
Who would've thought that
it could happen here?
It's so near us!
I mean, I thought we were safe
in this place.
Do we need to be careful
of the people around us?
Will you stop it?
You're scaring the kids.
I don't want to talk about
those kinds of stories,
especially at the dinner table.
Understood?
- Yes.
- Yes, Dad.
Come on.
Let's just eat.
We're trending!
There, Tirada is back
on top again.
It's a good thing
you were the first to come up
with this scoop.
No, of course, thanks to Kyle
and his friend, right?
I may be the one in front
of the screen,
but we all deserve the credit.
Great.
I think Berdugo's group
did that.
Because I remember before
that when someone collided
with Berdugo,
he would suddenly disappear.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Are you okay, Boss?
I was just thinking about
our report earlier.
I mean, which God has
the right to say,
to decide when a person
will die?
He just threw away the
victims like garbage, right?
As if the victim had no
personality, dreams, or family.
The person who did this
must have thought
that the bodies would never
be found.
There is no secret that goes
undiscovered.
That's why I think
that if Berdugo catches me,
that's definitely what
I'll end up with.
They'll torture me, kill me...
They'll put me in a bag,
then suddenly they'll dump me
somewhere.
Where no one can find me.
No trace. Not even a shadow
of me, nothing.
Just like what happened
to Godfather Diego.
He just disappeared all
of a sudden.
No one escapes from Berdugo.
He's that cruel.
You mean,
it's possible that one
of the bodies found
belongs to Godfather Diego?
It will eventually come out.
Whoever is behind this,
in our next report,
the hashtag we'll use
is "DemonyoReveal".
How did this happen?
There are celebrity vloggers
diving and found the corpses.
Don't worry,
I'll make them suffer.
Stupid!
The news will get hotter.
It'll get more attention.
I'm sorry, Boss.
But what are we going to do?
Should we just let them be?
We have no choice.
What you have to make sure
of is that those corpses
can't be connected to us.
It won't, Boss.
They definitely won't find
anything on those bodies.
You're being arrogant.
If this comes back to me,
I'll have someone throw you
next.
I told you,
I'll take care of it.
You really bought a lot.
And then, you spent a lot.
And you didn't report for work.
What's with you? I'm fine.
I'm on call.
Besides, Uncle will call me if
he needs me to do something.
And I won't leave you alone,
if you're not okay.
Thank you.
Good move.
At least, now, Andrew
is not overshadowing you.
Joey?
Where is Joey?
Andrew, why?
Joey, I went home as soon
as I found this out.
One of the bodies
has been identified
through dental records.
And, Joey, it's Major Aglipay.
It's confirmed.
Godfather?
Joey, no matter what happens,
don't go out, don't scream.
Go away now.
Theresa...
How did you meet this Lisa?
Online.
We matched profiles.
I messaged her, and she replied.
Give me your phone!
Here.
Hey, what do you want?
Are you still going to catch
Theresa?
Yes.
I saw a deactivated account
that links to Theresa.
I just need to pinpoint
the location of the IP address.
Then I'm sure that I will find
her there.
I just need to get my things.
So you're going to go home
to get it?
I'll go home with you.
I'll help you.
Aren't you supposed
to be with Joey?
Joey doesn't need me anymore.
Joey is with Andrew.
Meow!
Why did you meow? What was that?
Nothing. You know...
I just saw the video.
The sad boy like you.
Sad boy?
You know, because you've never
ever felt what I felt here.
What makes you say that?
Don't you know what I've been
through?
Okay. Fine, tell me.
Tell me what you've been
through.
Maybe next time.
Just go to Joey.
Go, Brother!
You know, Joey,
I know your Godfather Diego.
To this day,
I can't believe he was involved
in that syndicate.
Me too, Mom.
Even though Godfather Diego
wronged us,
he still didn't deserve
what happened to him.
I just hope he had at least a
little time to repent
and change his life.
Our contact at the precinct
said that the ashes
and Parak's belongings
were given to relatives.
What?
What we paid those idiots
is wasted
if they couldn't follow simple
orders.
All the belongings were checked
before they were released,
so they're safe.
That's not enough.
You have so many loose ends like
that Golda case.
You thought she was dead,
but she was still able to talk.
We have to make sure Parak
didn't leave anything else
behind.
If you need to find where
his belongings were taken,
that's what you do.
Mrs. Delgado,
as you and Miguel are listed
next of kin to Diego,
Major Aglipay's remains
will go to you,
as well as his office
belongings.
The entire police force
sympathizes with you.
- Thank you.
Please sit down.
- We'll put this away.
- Thank you.
I'll just put this on the altar,
okay?
We're working on it, Berdugo.
But just a thought...
since Diego has no family,
The next of kin are most likely
the Delgados.
Probably, Delgado's wife already
has the things.
Well, in that case,
I'll take care of it so I don't
hear any more failures.
Everything okay?
Yes.
I just remembered what you
told me
about our employee asking
for help.
It's slipped from my mind,
but I do want to help.
Clarissa?
Yes.
I want to meet her as soon
as possible.
- Okay, Ma'am. We'll go ahead.
- Be careful, okay?
Thank you.
Mom...
- Joey?
- Look at this.
I saw it on the sleeve
of Godfather Diego's jacket.
What am I going to do with it?
Mother, I think that's where
the evidence I'm looking for is.
That's why he put it there.
Why did you just tell me now?
Let's go after the Chief!
Let's give it to him!
- What?
- No Mom.
I've learned my lesson.
We need to see what's inside
before we surrender it.
Tomas, Clarissa.
I don't want to bother you
anymore.
There's new evidence
that just came out.
What evidence?
I'm working on a way
to find Theresa.
I'm hoping that it pays off
this time.
Delgado got some new evidence.
Find out right away what it is.
The question now, Ka-Tiradas,
is what will happen in the case
of Major Miguel Delgado,
who was first accused
of killing Ramon Orbos?
Andrew knows a lot
about Delgado.
What, Berdugo?
Should I include him in
what I'm cooking for Delgado?
Because of the evidence
that came out
in the case of Major
Miguel Delgado,
the court has already made
a decision, Ka-Tiradas.